rosenfeldmedia.com 2019-09-20

# Privacy Policy - Rosenfeld Media

## Rosenfeld Media LLC Privacy Policy

We hope you’ll find our books, conferences, and other products and services valuable to your work. And we hope you’ll let us know what we’ve done well and how we can do better. Our Privacy Policy addresses the kind of information we gather from our visitors and how we use it. If you have any questions, please contact us:

Rosenfeld Media LLC  
privacy@rosenfeldmedia.com  
540 President Street, 1st Floor  
Brooklyn, NY 11215 USA  
+1.718.568.9756

#### Your acceptance of our privacy policy

By using rosenfeldmedia.com, you agree to the collection and use by Rosenfeld Media, LLC of your personal information (“PI”) as described in this policy. If we make any significant changes to this policy, we will notify you by email, or by posting a notice of such changes on the site. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Rosenfeld Media LLC does not own or control and whose materials, content, goods, or services are accessed through the site.

#### What we collect about you that is personally identifiable

We collect your personal information including your name, email address, password, and other information that you specifically provide to us to set up your account, or subscribe to our newsletters and announcements, which information can be revised and deleted by you. All passwords are stored on our server in encrypted form. We also collect information you provide us in response to our inquiries; for example, (1) your physical address for delivery of books you have requested from us, (2) opinions, ideas, suggestions, and information in response to online surveys, (3) other information you have elected to provide Rosenfeld Media LLC, and (4) your physical address and billing information for conferences and training services that you purchase from us. This is an “opt-in” policy with regards to consenting to our collection and use of PI. Additionally, if you register for one of our conferences, we may provide your name, title, and company name to our conference sponsors and, if you opt in, your email address.

#### Other data we collect which is not personally-identifiable

We collect information regarding use of the site, such as login information, computer-related information (for example, browser type you used, your Internet Protocol address, last URL visited, and the date and time of day of your login). We send a “cookie” or “pixel tag” to your computer that contains an identification number that is unique to the computer you are using. You may decline to provide such information to us and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although some of our features or services may not function properly as a result.

#### How we use PI and other data

We use the information we gather to enhance the experience of using our site, to understand how our site is used, to customize advertising, to communicate with our users about information relating to the site, to investigate and verify proper conduct at the site, and for the security, integrity, quality improvement, and monitoring of the site. We use data in the aggregate for our business purposes, but we do not disclose such aggregate data in a manner that allows identification of an individual user. We may also use the information we gather to communicate with you about events, products, and services we believe may be of interest to you. You are free to opt-out of receiving such communications; to do so, please contact Rosenfeld Media (privacy@rosenfeldmedia.com).

#### Your rights under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

Regardless of any legal requirements otherwise, we will do our best to extend substantially the same or more stringent protections afforded our European Union (“EU”) customers to all of our customers worldwide. If you are a EU resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us (privacy@rosenfeldmedia.com). When you opt in to provide your PI, you are providing us with your consent to use that information, as described above.

Additionally, if you are an EU resident, we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through our site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to the United States.

For a complete listing of your GDPR rights, please view them [here](http://eur-lex.europa.eu/legal-content/EN/TXT/HTML/?uri=CELEX:32016R0679&from=en). 

#### Nondisclosure of PI

We will not disclose your PI to third parties without your permission unless required by law or unless you’ve already consented to our doing so.

_Dated: May 25, 2018_
